#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/steven-fu-76b46b4a (LinkedIn) www.pluginpassiveincome.com (Company) www.pluginpassiveincome.com/blog (Blog) feeds.feedburner.com/ InternetBusinessIdeasJobsOnline (Rss)

#### Top Skills

internet marketing, yoga, MMA, gas turbine surveillance & maintenance Team Management Business Management

# Languages

English

## Steven Fu

Fleet Manager at Rolls-Royce/AGTS Selangor

### Summary

I have more than 20 years of experience in gas turbine maintenance, modification, commissioning, operations and management in the Aviation, Commercial Power Generation Industries and Oil & Gas Industry. Currently with Rolls Royce/AGTS leading a team of Engineers and Managers to serve and meet my customers (Petronas/Exxon Mobil) goals and objectives.

Please view my experiences in the form below;

## Experience

Rolls-Royce/AGTS
Fleet Manager
July 2011 - Present (10 years 6 months)
Malaysia

Previously worked at; MAS (Malaysia Airlines), ABB, Alstom, Sembawang Corp Co-Generation.

Online Internet Success Business Owner 2007 - Present (14 years) Kuala Lumpur

Online SEO, PPC and Amazon Marketer with business reach all over the world. An online business coach who is currently working with Derek Gehl to build his IBA (Internet Business Accelerator) program in Malaysia.

Sembawang Corporation Co-Generation Engineer/Project Manager January 2000 - July 2007 (7 years 7 months) Singapore

Worked in the Operations for the commercial Power Generation division as a control room Engineer and later as a Project Manager for 2.5 years, in laying facilities pipe lines (includes; fire water, steam & demineralised water) to Sembcorp's customers and boiler commissioning in Sakra Island, Singapore.

ABB Power Malaysia Control Room Senior Technician January 1994 - July 2007 (13 years 7 months) KLPP, Malaysia

Involved in the erection and commissioning of 2x ABB 13E2 gas turbines, 2x HRSGs' and 1

Steam Turbine. As the Snr Technician, I am to ensure operation of the plant in the most cost effective and efficient manner, carry out trip analysis and assist in manpower planning and management during outages.

ABB Energy was later bought over by Alstom and I along with the whole team was automatically absorbed into Alstom.

MAS (Malaysia Airlines Sdn Bhd)
Artisan (Aircraft Mechanic)
July 1991 - January 1994 (2 years 7 months)
Subang Airport, Malaysia

Aircraft Artisan - Specializing in Gas Turbine maintenance and modification, worked on RB211, CFM 56C2, Pratt and Whitney & GE Aero engines (CF6 80's and CF6 50's engines). I was later promoted to a Production Planner - Scheduling and planning of engine modification, servicing and spares availability.

## Education

MAS Training School, Stamford College, Newport University Master of Business Administration (M.B.A.)